RISHIRAM KATWAL

Full Stack Developer

I am a Full-Stack Developer (MERN) specializing in technologies like Node.js, Express, MongoDB, and React. My focus on clean code and server-side architecture allows me to create efficient and reliable web applications. I like to play with things and learn new things to keep me updated and Passionate about problem-solving.

Contact

+977 9861334033

rramkatwal24@gmail.com

• Gokarneshwor, ktm

Education

University of SunderlandBSc (Hons) Computer

Systems Engineering ISMT (2019-2024)

Tinkune-Kathmandu

Sainik Awasiya Maha-Vidyalaya

NEB Science 2016-2018

Sallaghari-Bhaktapur

Language

Nepali

English

Hindi

Experiences

College Projects ISMT Tinkune - KTM

2019 - 2024

Library Management System(asp.net core MVC), Hotel Management System(Windows Form), Organic Farm (asp.net core MVC), Login/Registration (MERN stack), Fun Olympic website (MERN Stack)

MERN Stack Course

Broadway Infosys

march 2023 - july 2023

I went for the MERN stack course and built an e-commerce app, where I Developed APIs and business logic with Node.js, Express.js, and React for seamless integration and enhanced functionality.

MERN Stack Training
Saptacode Technology Private Limited

Soft Skills Technical Skills

Communication Node.js
Problem Solving React

Critical thinking MongoDB

Adaptability Express.js

Time Management Bootstarp

Teamwork CSS3

mwork CSS3 HTML5

Portfolio: https://rishiramkatwal.com.np/ **Github:** https://github.com/rramKatwal